A Guide to the Records of the Virginia Secretary of Health and Human Resources, 1997-2006 [bulk 2002-2005]
Library of Virginia
- Series II: Constituent Correspondence, 2000-2006 [bulk 2002-2005]
  - REVIEW: Constituent Correspondence 2001 Aug - undated (Box 78, Folder 5)
  - RESTRICTED: Constituent Correspondence, 2000114-2000115 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - RESTRICTED: Constituent Correspondence, 2000157-2000520 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - RESTRICTED: Constituent Correspondence, 2000521-2001271 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - RESTRICTED: Constituent Correspondence, 2001349-2002825 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - RESTRICTED: Constituent Correspondence, 2002827-2003807 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - RESTRICTED: Constituent Correspondence, 2003865-2005064 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - RESTRICTED: Constituent Correspondence, 2005065-2005689 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - RESTRICTED: Constituent Correspondence, 2005743-2007975 (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - RESTRICTED: Constituent Correspondence, 2008002-2011729 (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - RESTRICTED: Constituent Correspondence, 2011809-2012851 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - RESTRICTED: Constituent Correspondence, 2012854-2013971 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - RESTRICTED: Constituent Correspondence, 2013972-2016599 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - RESTRICTED: Constituent Correspondence, 2016719-2079176 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - RESTRICTED: Constituent Correspondence, 2019191-2020740 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - RESTRICTED: Constituent Correspondence, 2020890-2022264 (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - RESTRICTED: Constituent Correspondence, 2022285-2023312 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - RESTRICTED: Constituent Correspondence, 2023382 (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - RESTRICTED: Constituent Correspondence, 2023512-2026172 (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - RESTRICTED: Constituent Correspondence, 2026266-2030483 (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - RESTRICTED: Constituent Correspondence, 2030509-2032015 (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - RESTRICTED: Constituent Correspondence, 2032016-2033233 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - RESTRICTED: Constituent Correspondence, 2033310-2033977 (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - RESTRICTED: Constituent Correspondence, 2033974-2034532 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - RESTRICTED: Constituent Correspondence, 2034535-2035262 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - RESTRICTED: Constituent Correspondence, 2035280-2036375 (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - RESTRICTED: Constituent Correspondence, 2036394-2037035 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - RESTRICTED: Constituent Correspondence, 2037146-2038600 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - RESTRICTED: Constituent Correspondence, 2038697-2039711 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - RESTRICTED: Constituent Correspondence, 2039871-2040419 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - RESTRICTED: Constituent Correspondence, 2049099-2050697 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - RESTRICTED: Constituent Correspondence, 2050740-2053814 (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - RESTRICTED: Constituent Correspondence, 2053853-2057651 (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - RESTRICTED: Constituent Correspondence, 2057792-2061650 (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - RESTRICTED: Constituent Correspondence, 2062014-2067201 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - RESTRICTED: Constituent Correspondence, 2067233-2071733 (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - RESTRICTED: Constituent Correspondence, 2071808-2076489 (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - RESTRICTED: Constituent Correspondence, 2076880-2080829 (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - RESTRICTED: Constituent Correspondence, 2081013-2085449 (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - RESTRICTED: Constituent Correspondence, 2085636-2092055 (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - RESTRICTED: Constituent Correspondence, 2092664-2111093 (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - RESTRICTED: Constituent Correspondence, 2111464-2137750 (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - RESTRICTED: Constituent Correspondence, 2137808-2167319 (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - RESTRICTED: Constituent Correspondence, 2167341-2189824 (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - RESTRICTED: Constituent Correspondence, 2190158-2202695 (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - RESTRICTED: Constituent Correspondence, 2202978-2210851 (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - RESTRICTED: Constituent Correspondence, 2210980-2223400 (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - RESTRICTED: Constituent Correspondence, 2223482-2239278 (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - RESTRICTED: Constituent Correspondence, 2239278-2258098 (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - RESTRICTED: Constituent Correspondence, 2258775-2284783 (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - RESTRICTED: Constituent Correspondence, 2284783-2303023 (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - RESTRICTED: Constituent Correspondence, 2303107-2315273 (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - RESTRICTED: Constituent Correspondence, 2316084-2333825 (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - RESTRICTED: Constituent Correspondence, 2334087-2349461 (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - RESTRICTED: Constituent Correspondence, 2349508-2356087 (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - RESTRICTED: Constituent Correspondence, 2356105 (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - RESTRICTED: Constituent Correspondence, 2356227-2368815 (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - RESTRICTED: Constituent Correspondence, 2368923-2378266 (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - RESTRICTED: Constituent Correspondence, 2378267-2393100 (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - RESTRICTED: Constituent Correspondence, 2393136-2409967 (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - RESTRICTED: Constituent Correspondence, 2410017-2420679 (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - RESTRICTED: Constituent Correspondence, 2420775-2425744 (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - RESTRICTED: Constituent Correspondence, 2425038-2435910 (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - RESTRICTED: Constituent Correspondence, 2425965-2432885 (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - RESTRICTED: Constituent Correspondence, 2436163-2445495 (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - RESTRICTED: Constituent Correspondence, 2445552-2452475 (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - RESTRICTED: Constituent Correspondence, 2452475-2458577 (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - RESTRICTED: Constituent Correspondence, 2458595-2466842 (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - RESTRICTED: Constituent Correspondence, 2466862-2475515 (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - RESTRICTED: Constituent Correspondence, 2475534-2480689 (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - RESTRICTED: Constituent Correspondence, 2481139-2484639 (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - RESTRICTED: Constituent Correspondence, 2484699-2469774 (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - RESTRICTED: Constituent Correspondence, 2489786-2494395 (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - RESTRICTED: Constituent Correspondence, 2494517-2498783 (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - RESTRICTED: Constituent Correspondence, 2498823-2501928 (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - RESTRICTED: Constituent Correspondence, 2502027-2511501 (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - RESTRICTED: Constituent Correspondence, A (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - RESTRICTED: Constituent Correspondence, B (folder 1 of 3) (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - RESTRICTED: Constituent Correspondence, B (folder 2 of 3) (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - RESTRICTED: Constituent Correspondence, B (folder 3 of 3) (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - RESTRICTED: Constituent Correspondence, C (folder 1 of 2) (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - RESTRICTED: Constituent Correspondence, C (folder 2 of 2) (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - RESTRICTED: Constituent Correspondence, D (folder 1 of 2) (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - RESTRICTED: Constituent Correspondence, D (folder 2 of 2) (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - RESTRICTED: Constituent Correspondence, E (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - RESTRICTED: Constituent Correspondence, F (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - RESTRICTED: Constituent Correspondence, G (folder 1 of 3) (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - RESTRICTED: Constituent Correspondence, G (folder 2 of 3) (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - RESTRICTED: Constituent Correspondence, G (folder 3 of 3) (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - RESTRICTED: Constituent Correspondence, H (folder 1 of 4) (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - RESTRICTED: Constituent Correspondence, H (folder 2 of 4) (Box 51, Folder 5)
  - RESTRICTED: Constituent Correspondence, H (folder 3 of 4) (Box 51, Folder 6)
  - RESTRICTED: Constituent Correspondence, H (folder 4 of 4) (Box 51, Folder 7)
  - RESTRICTED: Constituent Correspondence, I (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - RESTRICTED: Constituent Correspondence, J (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - RESTRICTED: Constituent Correspondence, K (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - RESTRICTED: Constituent Correspondence, L (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - RESTRICTED: Constituent Correspondence, M (folder 1 of 3) (Box 52, Folder 5)
  - RESTRICTED: Constituent Correspondence, M (folder 2 of 3) (Box 52, Folder 6)
  - RESTRICTED: Constituent Correspondence, M (folder 3 of 3) (Box 52, Folder 7)
  - RESTRICTED: Constituent Correspondence, N (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - RESTRICTED: Constituent Correspondence, O (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - RESTRICTED: Constituent Correspondence, P (folder 1 of 2) (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - RESTRICTED: Constituent Correspondence, P (folder 2 of 2) (Box 53, Folder 4)
  - RESTRICTED: Constituent Correspondence, R (folder 1 of 3) (Box 53, Folder 5)
  - RESTRICTED: Constituent Correspondence, R (folder 2 of 3) (Box 53, Folder 6)
  - RESTRICTED: Constituent Correspondence, R (folder 3 of 3) (Box 54, Folder 1)
  - RESTRICTED: Constituent Correspondence, S (folder 1 of 4) (Box 54, Folder 2)
  - RESTRICTED: Constituent Correspondence, S (folder 2 of 4) (Box 54, Folder 3)
  - RESTRICTED: Constituent Correspondence, S (folder 3 of 4) (Box 54, Folder 4)
  - RESTRICTED: Constituent Correspondence, S (folder 4 of 4) (Box 54, Folder 5)
  - RESTRICTED: Constituent Correspondence, T (folder 1 of 2) (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - RESTRICTED: Constituent Correspondence, T (folder 2 of 2) (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - RESTRICTED: Constituent Correspondence, U (Box 55, Folder 3)
  - RESTRICTED: Constituent Correspondence, V (Box 55, Folder 4)
  - RESTRICTED: Constituent Correspondence, W (folder 1 of 3) (Box 55, Folder 5)
  - RESTRICTED: Constituent Correspondence, W (folder 2 of 3) (Box 55, Folder 6)
  - RESTRICTED: Constituent Correspondence, W (folder 3 of 3) (Box 55, Folder 7)
  - RESTRICTED: Constituent Correspondence, Y (Box 56, Folder 1)
  - RESTRICTED: Constituent Correspondence, Z (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - RESTRICTED: Constituent Correspondence, Loose materials, 2002 (Box 56, Folder 3)
- Series III: Correspondence, 1997-2006 [bulk 2001-2005]
  - 2004 Executive Agreements (Box 72, Folder 1)
  - 2005 Virginia Congressional Delegation Meeting, 2005 (Box 58, Folder 1)
  - 340B Drug-Pricing Program Report, 2003 (Box 71, Folder 1)
  - Academic Health Education Centers: Funding, 2003 (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - Administrative Dispute Resolution: Agency Contacts, 2002-2003 (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - Administrative, 2002-2004 (Box 61, Folder 2)
  - Adult Protective Services in the Commonwealth: Presentation for Joint Commission on Health Care, 2002 (Box 58, Folder 2)
  - Age-Friendly Communities, 2002-2003 (Box 57, Folder 1)
  - Agency Legislation, 2004 Session, 2003 (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - Agency Strategic Plans: Dept. of Aging - Dept. of Health (Box 57, Folder 2)
  - Agency Strategic Plans: Dept. of Health Professions - Dept. of Mental Health, Mental Retardation and Substance Abuse Services (Box 57, Folder 3)
  - Agency Strategic Plans: Dept. of Rehabilitative Services - Dept. of Social Services (Box 57, Folder 4)
  - Agency Strategic Plans: Secretary of Health and Human Resources (Box 57, Folder 5)
  - Aging Drug Assistance, 2002 (Box 70, Folder 1)
  - AIDS Drug Resistance Program, 2005 (Box 61, Folder 4)
  - Allocation Methods - CSA Workshop, 2002 (Box 62, Folder 1)
  - American Hospital Association, 2004 (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - American Lung Association of Virginia, 2004 (Box 61, Folder 6)
  - American Pain Society, 2002-2003 (Box 61, Folder 7)
  - American Public Human Services Association, 2004-2005 (Box 71, Folder 8)
  - Archiving, 2002-2005 (Box 70, Folder 2)
  - Assisted Living Facilities Regulation, 2005, fo. 1 fo 2 (Box 58, Folder 3)
  - Assisted Living Facilities Regulation, 2005, fo. 2 fo 2 (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - Association Health Plans, 2005 (Box 61, Folder 9)
  - At-Will Employees: Leave and Severance Policy, 2002-2003 (Box 70, Folder 3)
  - Audit, 2002-2003 (Box 61, Folder 10)
  - Auditor of Public Accounts, 2002-2005, fo. 1 of 4 (Box 61, Folder 11)
  - Auditor of Public Accounts, 2002-2005, fo. 2 of 4 (Box 61, Folder 12)
  - Auditor of Public Accounts, 2002-2005, fo. 3 of 4 (Box 61, Folder 13)
  - Auditor of Public Accounts, 2002-2005, fo. 4 of 4 (Box 61, Folder 14)
  - Baby Care Link, 2003 (Box 61, Folder 15)
  - Behavioral Health Care and Long-Term Care Subcommittee Meeting Materials, 2004 (Box 59, Folder 2)
  - Best Management Practices Division: A Brief Overview for the Governor's Cabinet, 2002 (Box 62, Folder 2)
  - Biotech Council, 2002 (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - Biotechnology Initiatives, 2002-2004 (Box 61, Folder 16)
  - Biotechnology Initiatives: Editors' and Reporters' Guide to Biotechnology, 2002-2003, 2002, fo. 1 of 3 (Box 62, Folder 3)
  - Biotechnology Initiatives: Editors' and Reporters' Guide to Biotechnology, 2002-2003, 2002, fo. 2 of 3 (Box 62, Folder 4)
  - Biotechnology Initiatives: Editors' and Reporters' Guide to Biotechnology, 2002-2003, 2002, fo. 3 of 3 (Box 62, Folder 5)
  - Bioterror, 2002-2003 (Box 71, Folder 2)
  - REVIEW: Bioterror, 2002-2003 (Box 157, Folder 3)
  - REVIEW: BioWatch: Template for Public Health Response Policy, 2003 (Box 157, Folder 4)
  - Birth-Related Neurological Injury Fund, 2003-2004 (Box 62, Folder 6)
  - Board Meetings, 2002, fo. 1 of 2 (Box 72, Folder 2)
  - Board Meetings, 2002, fo. 2 of 2 (Box 72, Folder 3)
  - Board/Commission Vacancies, 2002 (Box 73, Folder 1)
  - Briefing Documents for Governor Warner, 2002 (Box 72, Folder 4)
  - Broadlands Subpoena I, 2005, fo. 1 of 2 (Box 68, Folder 1)
  - Broadlands Subpoena I, 2005, fo. 2 of 2 (Box 68, Folder 2)
  - Budget Bill, 2005 (Box 63, Folder 1)
  - Budget Crisis, 2002 (Box 72, Folder 5)
  - Budget, 2002-2004 (Box 62, Folder 7)
  - Case Management Pilots - Locality Selection, 2003 (Box 63, Folder 2)
  - Center for Medicare and Medicaid Services, 2004 (Box 62, Folder 8)
  - Cervical Cancer, 2004-2005 (Box 61, Folder 17)
  - Charlotte County Community Policy Management Team, 2003-2004 (Box 59, Folder 3)
  - Charlotte County FAPT Alternative, 2004 (Box 73, Folder 2)
  - Child Care and Development Fund, 2002 (Box 59, Folder 4)
  - Child Health Investment Partnership, 2003-2004 (Box 62, Folder 9)
  - Child Support "Pass-Through" (Supplement), 2003-2004 (Box 62, Folder 10)
  - Childhood Obesity Initiatives, 2002-2003 (Box 57, Folder 6)
  - Children's Health System, Inc.: Administrative Regulation Review, undated (Box 61, Folder 18)
  - Children's Hospital, 2004 (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - Chronological File, 2002 (Box 70, Folder 4)
  - Chronological File, 2003, fo. 1 of 2 (Box 70, Folder 5)
  - Chronological File, 2003, fo. 2 of 2 (Box 70, Folder 6)
  - REVIEW: Chronological File, 2003 (Box 157, Folder 5)
  - Chronological File, 2003-2005 (Box 70, Folder 7)
  - Commonwealth Accounting Policies and Procedures, 2004 (Box 62, Folder 11)
  - Commonwealth of Virginia and Venture Philanthropy Partners, undated (Box 57, Folder 7)
  - Community Health Centers, 2005 (Box 61, Folder 19)
  - Comprehensive Services Act - DPB Objectives, 2004 (Box 73, Folder 3)
  - Comprehensive Services Act for At- Risk Youth and Families (CSA) State Executive Council Bylaws, 2003 (Box 73, Folder 5)
  - Comprehensive Services Act for At-Risk Youth and Families, 2005 (Box 74, Folder 1)
  - Comprehensive Services Act Presentation to House Appropriations Committee, 2003-2004 (Box 73, Folder 4)
  - Comprehensive State Plan 2006-2012: Virginia Department of Mental Health, Mental Retardation and Substance Abuse Services, 2005 (Box 61, Folder 20)
  - Conference on the Uninsured, 2004 (Box 62, Folder 1)
  - Congressional Briefing Material: 108th Congress, 2nd Session, 2004 (Box 58, Folder 5)
  - Congressional Briefing, 2003 (Box 73, Folder 6)
  - Congressional Briefing, 2004 (Box 73, Folder 7)
  - Congressional Delegation, 2002-2004 (Box 62, Folder 13)
  - Consolidate Deaf and Blind Schools, 2004 (Box 62, Folder 14)
  - Consolidated Mail Services, 2003-2004 (Box 73, Folder 8)
  - Constitutent Issues, 2002 (Box 76, Folder 1)
  - Constituent Issues, 2003 (Box 76, Folder 1)
  - Constituent Services, 2002-2004 (Box 69, Folder 1)
  - Construction of SVP Facility, 2003-2004 (Box 74, Folder 2)
  - Consumer-Driven Healthcare: Current Status and Potential for Public Sector, 2000-2001 (Box 58, Folder 6)
  - Contacts, 2002-2005 (Box 69, Folder 2)
  - Continuity of Coperations Plans, 2002-2005 (Box 62, Folder 16)
  - REVIEW: Continuity of Coperations Plans, 2002-2005 (Box 157, Folder 6)
  - Coordinated Data Collection, 2002 (Box 62, Folder 17)
  - Coordinated School Health Program, 2004 (Box 60, Folder 3)
  - Coordinating Contracting of Prescription Drugs: A Fiscal and Policy Strategy for the Commonwealth of Virginia, 2003 (Box 61, Folder 21)
  - Copies from NLR "Sent File", 2005 (Box 68, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, 2002-2003 (Box 70, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, 2002-2004 (Box 76, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, 2002-2006 (Box 76, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, 2004 (Box 69, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, 2004-2005 (Box 76, Folder 3)
  - Council on the Status of Women, 2002-2003 (Box 65, Folder 1)
  - Council on Virginia's Future, 2003 (Box 58, Folder 7)
  - Council on Virginia's Future, 2003 (Box 58, Folder 8)
  - Council on Virginia's Future, 2003 (Box 65, Folder 2)
  - COVANET, 2004 (Box 65, Folder 3)
  - CPMT, 2003 (Box 73, Folder 9)
  - CPMT [2], 2003 (Box 73, Folder 10)
  - CPMT Chair Meeting, 8 May 2003 (Box 63, Folder 3)
  - Crossover Claims, 2003-2004 (Box 57, Folder 8)
  - CSA, undated (Box 59, Folder 5)
  - CSA: Childrens' Services Pilot, 2003-2004 (Box 62, Folder 18)
  - CSA: Concerns - Local Coordinators / Officials, 2002 (Box 63, Folder 4)
  - CSA: IVE Followup, 2002-2003 (Box 63, Folder 5)
  - CSA: Local Concerns, 2003 (Box 73, Folder 11)
  - CSA: Managed Care Ideas/Contacts, 2002-203, fo. 1 of 3 (Box 63, Folder 6)
  - CSA: Managed Care Ideas/Contacts, 2002-2003, fo. 2 of 3 (Box 63, Folder 7)
  - CSA: Managed Care Ideas/Contacts, 2002-2003, fo. 3 of 3 (Box 63, Folder 8)
  - CSA: Medicaid Data, undated (Box 62, Folder 19)
  - CSA: Medicaid Followup (New Levels of Care), 2003 (Box 63, Folder 9)
  - CSA: Organization Workshop, 2002 (Box 62, Folder 20)
  - CSA: Performance Standards, undated (Box 63, Folder 10)
  - CSA: Planning, 2002 (Box 63, Folder 11)
  - CSA: Portsmouth, 2001-2002 (Box 62, Folder 21)
  - CSA: Presentations, 2002 (Box 63, Folder 12)
  - CSA: Private Providers - Rate Setting, 2001-2002 (Box 62, Folder 22)
  - CSA: Projection of Service Needs (workgroup), 2002 (Box 62, Folder 23)
  - CSA: Quality of Care / Monitoring Workshop, 2002 (Box 62, Folder 24)
  - CSA: Report - Next Steps, 2002 (Box 63, Folder 13)
  - CSA: Service Fee Directory, 2002 (Box 62, Folder 25)
  - CSA: Steering Committee, 2002 (Box 70, Folder 9)
  - CSA: Updated, 2002 (Box 62, Folder 26)
  - CSA-Related Bills/OA Session, 2004 (Box 73, Folder 12)
  - Curriculum Resource Guide for Nutrition and Physical Activity Classies (Aligned with 2001 Virginia SOLs), 2003 (Box 58, Folder 9)
  - Data Warehouse, 2002 (Box 65, Folder 4)
  - Data Warehouse, 2002-2003 (Box 58, Folder 10)
  - Decision Brief, 2003-2005 (Box 65, Folder 5)
  - Decision Briefs, 2004 (Box 73, Folder 13)
  - Delegates, 2004-2005 (Box 65, Folder 6)
  - Department for the Blind and Visually Handicapped, 2005 (Box 74, Folder 3)
  - Department of Health Professions, 2005 [1] (Box 74, Folder 5)
  - Department of Health Professions, 2005 [2] (Box 61, Folder 23)
  - Department of Health Professions: Study into the Need to Regulate Natruopaths in Virginia, 2005 (Box 61, Folder 24)
  - Department of Health, 2005 [1] (Box 61, Folder 22)
  - Department of Health, 2005 [2] (Box 74, Folder 4)
  - Department of Medical Assistance Services, 2004-2005 (Box 61, Folder 25)
  - Department of Medical Assistance Services, 2005, fo. 1 of 2 (Box 74, Folder 6)
  - Department of Medical Assistance Services, 2005, fo. 2 of 2 (Box 74, Folder 7)
  - Department of Medical Assistance Services: Medicare Prescription Drug Benefit Program Part D: Training Videoconference, 2005 (Box 61, Folder 26)
  - Department of Mental Health, Mental Retardation and Substance Abuse Services, 205 (Box 61, Folder 27)
  - Department of Social Services, 2005 (Box 74, Folder 8)
  - Department of Social Services: Briefing Documents for Governor Warner, 2002 (Box 60, Folder 3)
  - Digital Healthcare, Inc., 2004-2005 (Box 65, Folder 7)
  - Directors Notes, 2002-2003 (Box 57, Folder 9)
  - Disability Navigator, 2003 (Box 57, Folder 10)
  - Draft Letter to Dr. Lynton Land, 2004 (Box 65, Folder 8)
  - DRS: Order of Selection, undated (Box 74, Folder 9)
  - Drug Court, 2003 (Box 59, Folder 6)
  - Drug Courts, 2002 (Box 74, Folder 10)
  - Due Diligence (Special Projects), 2002-2003 (Box 72, Folder 6)
  - Early Learning Council, 2004-2005 (Box 58, Folder 11)
  - Early Learning Council, 2005 (Box 58, Folder 12)
  - Early Periodic Screening Diagnosis and Treatment (EPSDT), 2004 (Box 65, Folder 10)
  - Electronic Health Records, Executive Directive 6, 2005 (Box 69, Folder 4)
  - REVIEW: Emergency Contact Info., 2002 (Box 157, Folder 7)
  - Emergency Preparedness, 2003-2004 (Box 65, Folder 9)
  - eVA, 2003 (Box 65, Folder 11)
  - REVIEW: Evergreene Nursing Home, 2005 (Box 157, Folder 8)
  - Executive Agreements, 2002 (Box 72, Folder 7)
  - Executive Directive 2 - Governor's Work Gropu on Rural Obstetrical Care, 2004 (Box 60, Folder 5)
  - Executive Directive 5 - Cervical Cancer, 2005 (Box 65, Folder 12)
  - Executive Order 16, 2002 (Box 72, Folder 9)
  - Executive Order 29, 2002, fo. 1 of 2 (Box 72, Folder 10)
  - Executive Order 29, 2002, fo. 2 of 2 (Box 72, Folder 11)
  - Executive Order 6 - Agency Submissions, 2002 (Box 72, Folder 8)
  - Executive Orders - WIA, 2002 (Box 70, Folder 10)
  - Expansion of Affordable, Accessible Housing for Persons with Disabilities and Frail Elders Statewide, 2003 (Box 57, Folder 11)
  - EZ-Filer Systems, 2005 (Box 76, Folder 5)
  - Faith-Based Initiatives, 2003 (Box 72, Folder 12)
  - Fatherhood / Family Strengthening Grants, 2002-2003 (Box 62, Folder 27)
  - Federal Reimbursement - CSA Workshop, 2002 (Box 62, Folder 28)
  - Financial Statement, 2004 (Box 65, Folder 13)
  - First Health - Department of Medical Assistance Services, 2002 (Box 60, Folder 6)
  - Flu, etc., 2004 (Box 65, Folder 14)
  - Follow-up on CSA Study Status Reprots, 2003, fo. 1 of 2 (Box 73, Folder 14)
  - Follow-up on CSA Study Status Reprots, 2003, fo. 2 of 2 (Box 73, Folder 15)
  - Food and Drug Administration (FDA) Commission, 2003 (Box 65, Folder 15)
  - Freedom of Information Act (FOIA), 2002-2005 (Box 65, Folder 16)
  - Freedom of Information Act Request, 2005 (Box 76, Folder 6)
  - Freedom of Information Act, 2005, fo. 1 of 2 (Box 64, Folder 1)
  - Freedom of Information Act, 2005, fo. 2 of 2 (Box 64, Folder 2)
  - General, 2002-2005, fo. 1 of 2 (Box 65, Folder 17)
  - General, 2002-2005, fo. 2 of 2 (Box 65, Folder 18)
  - REVIEW: General, 2002-2005 [1] (Box 158, Folder 1)
  - REVIEW: General, 2002-2005 [2] (Box 158, Folder 2)
  - General, 2003-2005, fo. 1 of 2 (Box 65, Folder 19)
  - General, 2003-2005, fo. 2 of 2 (Box 65, Folder 29)
  - General Correspondence, 2005 (Box 61, Folder 28)
  - General: Discount Prescription Drug Plans, 2003 (Box 65, Folder 21)
  - Geriatric Services Restructuring, 2002 (Box 73, Folder 16)
  - Governor's Conference on Aging, 2003-2005 (Box 60, Folder 7)
  - Governor's Education Summit: Committee on Research, undated, fo. 1 of 2 (Box 59, Folder 7)
  - Governor's Education Summit: Committee on Research, undated, fo. 2 of 2 (Box 59, Folder 8)
  - Governor's Electronic Health Records Task Force, Preliminary Directive 6: Preliminary Report, 2005 (Box 61, Folder 29)
  - Governor's Fellow Program, 2003-2005 (Box 65, Folder 22)
  - Governor's Partnership for Achieving Successful Schools (PASS), 2002-2004 (Box 59, Folder 9)
  - Governor's Task Force on Cervical Cancer, 2005 (Box 59, Folder 10)
  - Grants, 2003-2005 (Box 65, Folder 23)
  - Greater Richmond Chamber of Commerce - Youth Matters, 2004 (Box 65, Folder 24)
  - REVIEW: Gupta Case, 2003 (Box 158, Folder 3)
  - Hamption Healthy Start, 2003 (Box 62, Folder 29)
  - Health and Human Resources Study: An Examination of the Role and Responsibilities of the Office of the Inspector General, 2002-204 (Box 66, Folder 1)
  - Health and Human Resources, 2005 (Box 74, Folder 11)